HEY, REMEMBER
WHEN I HAD A MONKEY?
YEAH.
MM-HMM.
YEAH, WHAT...
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
HEY, SO...
WHAT'S WITH THE 20% TIP?
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
20% IS A PRETTY
GENEROUS TIP, JOE.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT'S
MORE GENEROUS THAN THAT? 50%.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
EVEN MORE GENEROUS THAN THAT?
I SEE WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
WHAT'S UP
WITH THE GREED, JOE?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS
BUT IT'S JUST
THAT I GOT TO GET
THESE NEW HEAD SHOTS MADE,
AND THEY'RE REALLY EXPENSIVE
YOU KNOW?
I'M DOWN TO, LIKE, THREE.
ACTUALLY, TWO
'CAUSE ONE OF THEM
I KIND OF BLACKENED IN
SOME TEETH.
WHY'D I DO THAT?
GOD!
WELL, ISN'T THERE
SOMETHING YOU CAN DO
TO EARN A LITTLE
EXTRA MONEY?
I MEAN, CAN'T
YOU PICK UP...
I DON'T KNOW,
AN EXTRA SHIFT HERE?
OR... YOU KNOW, I USED
TO BEG FOR MONEY.
OF COURSE, IT HELPS
IF YOU'VE GOT A LITTLE
OF THIS GOING ON.
WOW. I STILL HAVE IT.
Joey:
YEAH.
OH, WAIT, WAIT. DON'T YOU
HAVE AN AUDITION TODAY?
YEAH, MAYBE
YOU'LL GET THAT JOB.
OH, HA, HA, HA.
OOH!
WAIT A MINUTE-- I USED TO GET
MEDICAL EXPERIMENTS
DONE ON ME ALL THE TIME.
AH, FINALLY AN EXPLANATION.
NO, NO, I USED TO GET PAID
FOR ALL KINDS
OF MEDICAL STUFF, REMEMBER?
LET'S SEE, UH... WELL, I DON'T
WANT TO DONATE SPERM AGAIN.
I REALLY PREFER DOING THAT
AT THE HOME OFFICE, YOU KNOW.
OOH, OOH!
MAYBE THEY WANT SOME OF MY BLOOD
OR SPIT OR SOMETHING, HUH?
JOEY.
YEAH.
WHAT'D I TELL YOU
ABOUT TALKING TO YOUR FRIENDS
WHILE YOU'RE WORKING?
UH... DO IT?
THAT GUY'S BEEN WAITING
FOR HIS COFFEE FOR TEN MINUTES.
HE'S COMPLAINED ABOUT YOU
THREE TIMES.
WELL, WHERE WAS I?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HI.
HEY.
HEY, WHAT HAVE YOU
GUYS BEEN UP TO?
OH, WE WENT TO A SELF-DEFENSE
CLASS TODAY.
WOW.
YEAH.
KICKING A GUY IN THE
CROTCH ALL MORNING
REALLY TAKES IT
OUT OF YOU.
TAKES IT OUT OF YOU?
NO, NOW WE CAN KICK
ANYBODY'S ASS.
YEAH.
AFTER ONE CLASS?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT? YOU WANT TO SEE ME
SELF-DEFEND MYSELF?
GO OVER THERE AND PRETEND
YOU'RE A SEXUAL PREDATOR.
GO ON, I DARE YOU!
WELL, OF COURSE,
YOU CAN DEFEND YOURSELF
FROM AN ATTACK
YOU KNOW IS COMING.
THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
LOOK, I STUDIED KAR-ATEY
FOR A LONG TIME
AND THERE'S
A CONCEPT
YOU SHOULD
REALLY BE FAMILIAR WITH.
IT'S WHAT THE JAPANESE
CALL UNAGI.
ISN'T THAT A KIND OF SUSHI?
NO, IT'S A CONCEPT.
YEAH, IT IS. IT IS.
IT'S FRESHWATER EEL.
ALL RIGHT,
MAYBE IT MEANS THAT, TOO.
OH, I WOULD KILL
FOR A SALMON SKIN
ROLL RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, FINE, GET ATTACKED;
I DON'T EVEN CARE.
( sighs )
COME ON, ROSS. WE'RE SORRY.
PLEASE TELL US WHAT IT IS.
UNAGI IS A STATE
OF TOTAL AWARENESS, OKAY?
ONLY BY ACHIEVING TRUE UNAGI
CAN YOU BE PREPARED
FOR ANY DANGER
THAT MAY BEFALL YOU.
YOU MEAN, IN CASE
SOMEONE'S TRYING TO STEAL
YOUR BAMBOO SLEEPING MAT
OR YOUR KETTLE OF FISH?
( mocking laughter )
ALL I'M SAYING IS,
IT'S ONE THING
BEING PREPARED
FOR AN ATTACK AGAINST,
LIKE, EACH OTHER.
WHOLE 'NOTHER STORY
BEING PREPARED
FOR AN ATTACK
I DON'T KNOW,
LIKE, A SURPRISE!
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNEW
THAT WAS COMING
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE UNAGI.
OOH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF WE MADE RESERVATIONS
WE COULD HAVE UNAGI
IN ABOUT A HALF HOUR.
YOU KNOW WHAT...?
HEY, HEY, IS MONICA HERE?
NO. UH-UH.
LOOK, I NEED YOUR HELP--
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO GET HER
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY.
WELL, VALENTINE'S DAY
WAS TWO WEEKS AGO
SO I WOULDN'T
GET HER A CALENDAR.
( weak chuckle )
SHE WAS WORKING
ON VALENTINE'S DAY
SO WE'RE CELEBRATING
IT TONIGHT.
OH, HEY, WHY DON'T YOU
BOOK A DAY FOR BOTH OF YOU
AT ONE OF THOSE
ROMANTIC SPAS?
OOH, JOEY, THAT'S ACTUALLY
A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
YEAH, AND, OF COURSE,
CROTCHLESS PANTIES.
WELL, AS APPEALING
AS THAT DOES SOUND
TO HER BOYFRIEND...
AND HER BROTHER...
I CAN'T DO THAT.
WE PROMISED WE'D MAKE
EACH OTHER GIFTS THIS YEAR.
OH, I LOVE THAT.
YOU GUYS!
YOU CAN'T MAKE
CROTCHLESS PANTIES?
YOU TAKE...
YOU TAKE A PAIR OF SCISSORS
AND JUST CUT THE...
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY!
SO, MAKING THINGS--
THAT SOUNDS SO MUCH FUN.
YEAH, I THOUGHT SO, TOO
UNTIL I PAPIER-MACHE'D
ONE OF MY EYES SHUT.
I LOVE PAPIER-MACHE.
WHAT DID YOU MAKE?
I MADE A ( gibberish ).
WHAT IS THAT?
NOTHING!
OH.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WELL, HAVE YOU GUYS
MADE ANYTHING
THAT MAYBE
I COULD TAKE CREDIT FOR?
OOH, I HAVE. I HAVE.
UM, I STARTED MAKING
THESE LITTLE SOCK BUNNIES.
OH, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
LOOK.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT IS MY SOCK.
NOW IT'S YOUR
LITTLE BUNNY FRIEND.
( both laughing )
OKAY.
THIS... THIS ACTUALLY
IS A ( gibberish ).
HEY!
HEY.
HONEY, CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION
ABOUT THE VALENTINE'S DAY GIFTS?
OH, YEAH.
DO WE HAVE TO MAKE
THE ENTIRE THING?
YES.
WHY, DID YOU FORGET
TO MAKE YOURS?
OF COURSE... OF COURSE NOT.
I JUST HAVE TO, UH...
GO OVER TO THE PLACE WHERE
I MADE IT AND PICK IT UP.
OKAY. I CAN'T WAIT.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
THE BEST VALENTINE'S DAY EVER.
( nervous laughter )
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
MAKE THE PRESENTS!
WHAT?
I'M JUST SO EXCITED
TO MAKE THE PRESENTS!
( nervous laughter )
SHOOT!
HI. UH, I'M JOEY TRIBBIANI
AND, WITH ALL
DUE RESPECT
I'D LIKE TO
DONATE SOME FLUIDS.
WE'RE ACTUALLY AT THE END
OF ONE OF OUR RESEARCH CYCLES
SO WE'RE NOT LOOKING
FOR APPLICANTS RIGHT NOW.
OH, THAT'S TOO BAD;
I KIND OF BEEN SAVING UP.
UH... ARE YOU SURE
THERE'S NO STUDIES
I COULD PARTICIPATE IN?
WELL, HERE'S A SCHEDULE
OF WHAT'S COMING UP.
AH, THANKS.
BUT THIS ONE
STARTS NOW.
OH, THAT ONE
IS AVAILABLE NOW
BUT ONLY IDENTICAL TWINS
ARE ELIGIBLE; IT'S A TWIN STUDY.
BUT IT'S $2,000.
SORRY.
OH.
AND, WELL, HOW
ABOUT THIS ONE?
"TESTING THE EFFECTS
OF JOEY TRIBBIANI
ON ATTRACTIVE NURSE
RECEPTIONIST."
WE ALREADY GOT
THE RESULTS BACK ON THAT ONE
AND THEY'RE NOT GOOD.
...BUT IT WAS GOOD.
THOSE LAST MOVES WERE...
DANGER! DANGER!
ROSS!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?!
A LESSON IN THE IMPORTANCE
OF UNAGI.
OH!
YOU'RE A FREAK!
PERHAPS.
NOW, I'M CURIOUS--
AT WHAT POINT
DURING THOSE GIRLISH SCREAMS
WOULD YOU HAVE BEGUN
TO "KICK MY ASS"?
ALL RIGHT, SO WE
WEREN'T PREPARED.
I'M SORRY I HAD TO TAKE
SUCH DRASTIC MEASURES
TO MAKE MY POINT
BUT, LOOK, I JUST WANT
YOU GUYS TO BE SAFE.
OH.
DANGER!
UH-HUH.
UNAGI.
2,000 BUCKS IS A LOT OF MONEY.
BOY, I WISH I HAD A TWIN.
WHERE COULD I FIND SOMEONE...
WHO LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE ME?
HEY.
CHANDLER...
I SENSED IT WAS YOU.
WHAT?
UNAGI.
I'M ALWAYS AWARE.
OKAY, ARE YOU AWARE
THAT UNAGI IS AN EEL?
WHAT'S UP?
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO MAKE MONICA.
WHY NOT MAKE HER ONE
OF YOUR LITTLE JOKES?
I'M GOING CRAZY, OKAY?
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
AROUND HERE
THAT LOOKS HOMEMADE?
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE'D LOVE THIS.
IT'S AN EXACT REPLICA
OF APOLLO EIGHT.
I MADE IT IN THE SIXTH GRADE.
YEAH, I GUESS
I COULD USE THAT.
I COULD SAY, "YOUR LOVE
SENDS ME TO THE MOON."
YEAH, YEAH.
EXCEPT APOLLO EIGHT DIDN'T
ACTUALLY LAND ON THE MOON.
BUT YOU COULD WRITE
"YOUR LOVE LETS ME
ORBIT THE MOON TWICE
AND RETURN SAFELY."
WAIT A MINUTE, I CAN'T
GIVE THIS TO HER.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE IT SAYS "CAPTAIN
ROSS" ON THE SIDE...
AND IT SAYS "I HATE
MONICA" ON THE BOTTOM.
MM-HMM.
DANGER!
( high-pitched shriek )
AH...
SALMON SKIN ROLL.
OKAY... OKAY...
YES, HONEY, I'VE MADE IT MYSELF.
I CAN'T DO IT.
OH! OH!
A MIX TAPE! A MIX TAPE!
OKAY, HI.
UH, YOU READY TO
EXCHANGE GIFTS?
SURE.
OKAY, YOU GO FIRST.
OKAY, COME HERE.
COME HERE.
OKAY.
NOW, IT'S NOT WRAPPED
BECAUSE I JUST,
JUST FINISHED IT.
OKAY.
BUT I MADE YOU A TAPE
OF WHAT I THINK
ARE ALL ROMANTIC SONGS.
( gasping )
WHAT A GREAT GIFT.
IS "THE WAY YOU LOOK
TONIGHT" ON IT?
MAYBE. WE'LL HAVE
TO LISTEN AND SEE.
OH, I LOVE IT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
OKAY.
YOU READY TO
OPEN YOURS?
YEAH.
OKAY.
IT'S A SOCK BUNNY.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU REMEMBER
HOW I CALL YOU "BUNNY"?
NOT REALLY.
WELL, I DID ONE TIME
AND I WANT TO START
DOING IT MORE.
SEE, THAT'S WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT.
I SEE.
YOU KNOW, UM...
PHOEBE MAKES SOCK BUNNIES.
NO, NO, SHE DOESN'T.
PHOEBE, WHAT SHE MAKES,
THEY'RE SOCK RABBITS.
THEY'RE COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT.
OKAY! OKAY!
OKAY
I DIDN'T MAKE IT.
I'M SORRY.
I TOTALLY FORGOT ABOUT TONIGHT
AND THE FACT THAT WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO MAKE THE PRESENTS.
OH, IT'S OKAY. I DON'T, I...
NO, NO, IT'S NOT OKAY.
IT'S NOT.
I MEAN, YOU WERE JUST...
YOU'RE SO INCREDIBLE
AND YOU WENT THROUGH
ALL THIS TIME AND EFFORT TO MAKE
THIS TAPE FOR ME;
YOU KNOW, I'M
JUST GOING TO...
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE
THIS UP TO YOU-- I WILL.
I AM GOING TO... COOK YOU
ANYTHING YOU WANT IN HERE
AND I'M GOING TO DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT IN THERE.
WELL, I DID PUT
A LOT OF THOUGHT INTO THE TAPE.
WOW.
YOU ARE WAY TOO YOUNG
TO HAVE SEEN THAT.
YOU KNOW, YOUR BIRTHDAY'S
IN A MONTH AND A HALF.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
I FORGET TO GET YOU
A PRESENT FOR THAT TOO?
YOU ARE TOTALLY AND
COMPLETELY 100% FORGIVEN.
WE HAVE GOT TO WASH THAT.
YEAH.
HEY.
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT JACKET
THAT YOU LOVED SO MUCH
THAT YOU THOUGHT
WAS TOO EXPENSIVE?
YOU HAVE DONE ENOUGH.
I'M GOING TO WAKE UP EARLY
AND GO GET IT FOR YOU.
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE... GET
IT IN BLACK, NOT BROWN.
( bell dings )
OOP! YOUR CAKE IS READY.
OOP.
WELL, IT'S LIKE
THAT OLD SAYING--
"HAVE SEX,
EAT SOME CAKE."
HEY, MON. HEY, CHAN.
JUST GETTING A SODA.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
I'M JOEY.
HOW ARE YOU DOIN'?
NO! NO! NO! NO! NO!
HOW YOU DOIN'?
DAMN IT, CARL.
GO WAIT IN THE HALL.
LOOK.
I'VE GOT TO APOLOGIZE
ON BEHALF OF CARL.
WHO THE HELL IS CARL?!
OH, DID I NOT MENTION?
CARL
IS A GUY I HIRED
TO BE MY IDENTICAL TWIN
FOR A MEDICAL RESEARCH
PROJECT.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES
THE GOOD IDEAS ARE
JUST RIGHT IN FRONT
OF YOU, AREN'T THEY?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY,
BUT I THINK IT MIGHT WORK
BUT THE ONLY PROBLEM IS,
CARL'S ACTING IS...
THE ONLY PROBLEM?
YEAH, HE'S THE REASON
I DIDN'T GET
THAT BIG MINUTE MAID
COMMERCIAL
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO,
REMEMBER?
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO BE BROTHERS,
BUT HE MESSED IT UP.
HEY.
UH, CAN I GET A LITTLE PIECE
OF THAT CAKE?
PIZZA! WE LIKE PIZZA!
GET OUT!
PAT SAJAK?
YEAH.
ALEX TREBEK?
OH, OF COURSE.
CHUCK WOOLERY.
DEFINITELY, PHOEBE.
YOU WILL NOT FIND
A SINGLE GAME SHOW HOST
WHOSE ASS I CANNOT KICK.
( groaning in pain )
SAY IT!
SAY "WE ARE UNAGI."
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU ARE;
IT'S SOMETHING YOU HAVE.
SAY IT!
YOU KNOW, I COULD EASILY
GET OUT OF THIS
BUT THERE'S A CHANCE
YOU COULD GET VERY, VERY HURT.
( screaming )
ALL RIGHT, CARL, WE'RE NEXT.
NOW REMEMBER
WHAT IS THIS
NOT GOING TO BE?
ANOTHER MINUTE
MAID FIASCO.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND WHAT ARE YOU
NOT GOING TO DO?
I'M NOT GOING TO TALK BECAUSE...
THAT... DAMN IT, CARL!
( warning grunt )
CAN I HAVE THE NEXT ONE,
PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
JOEY AND TONY TRIBBIANI.
THAT'S US.
BUT, UH...
THIS IS A STUDY
FOR IDENTICAL TWINS.
THAT'S RIGHT--
$2,000.
BUT YOU'RE NOT IDENTICAL TWINS.
DAMN IT, CARL!
OH, MY GOOD GOD.
OKAY, CONTINUING
THE COUNTDOWN
OF YOUR FAVORITE MEALS.
TONIGHT, NUMBER THREE:
MACARONI AND CHEESE
WITH CUT-UP HOT DOGS.
LOOK, YOU HAVE DONE
ENOUGH, OKAY?
YOU HAVE TO STOP THIS NOW.
I WILL BUT NOT TONIGHT.
AND FOR DINNER MUSIC,
I THOUGHT
WE COULD LISTEN TO THAT
TAPE THAT YOU MADE ME.
OH, THE MIX TAPE.
Tony Bennett:
♪ When I'm awfully low... ♪
"THE WAY YOU LOOK TONIGHT"
IS ON HERE.
DANCE WITH ME?
♪ I will feel a glow
just thinking of you ♪
♪ And the way
you look tonight. ♪
YOU ARE JUST
THE SWEETEST...
Janice:
I love the way you look
every night, Chandler.
That's why I made you this tape.
Happy Birthday!
Love, Janice.
( kissing sound )
NO, YOU'RE THE SWEETEST...
OKAY, LADIES, THAT ENDS TODAY'S
CLASS, AND LET'S REMEMBER--
LET'S BE SAFE OUT THERE.
IT'S A GREAT CLASS.
THANKS, MAN.
YEAH, YEAH,
I WAS WATCHING.
UM, HEY, A COUPLE
OF QUESTIONS, THOUGH.
UM, YOU KNOW,
ABOUT THAT LAST MOVE
WHERE THAT WOMAN TRIPPED YOU
AND THEN PINNED YOU
TO THE FLOOR?
WHAT WOULD YOU DO NEXT?
WELL, AND THEN SHE'D TAKE
HER KEYS AND TRY TO JAM THEM...
NO, NO,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO NEXT?
WHO, ME, THE ATTACKER?
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
WHY?
I TRIED ATTACKING TWO WOMEN.
DID NOT WORK.
WHAT?
NO, I MEAN, IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, THEY'RE MY FRIENDS.
IN FACT, I WAS MARRIED
TO ONE OF THEM.
LET ME GET
THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU ATTACKED YOUR EX-WIFE?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I TRIED
BUT I COULDN'T.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
MAYBE WE COULD ATTACK THEM
TOGETHER.
THAT'S A "NO."
I AM SO, SO,
SO, SO SORRY.
UH-HUH.
OH! AND I WILL COOK
ANYTHING YOU WANT IN HERE
AND DO ANYTHING YOU WANT
IN THERE.
YEAH, YOU WILL,
AND ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
OH, COME ON, MONICA,
IT'S OUR VALENTINE'S DAY.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE?
OKAY.
OKAY?
Janice:
♪ My funny valentine... ♪
SO ARE WE GOING IN THERE?
I AM.
AHA.
NOWHERE TO RUN.
I DON'T LIKE
SITTING UP HERE.
I'M GOING OVER THERE.
NO, RACHEL,
THEY GOT HERE FIRST.
WHAT?
WHY IS ROSS DOING THAT?
Ross:
DANGER!
OH, MY GOD!
WHY IS HE JUMPING
ON THOSE WOMEN?
WE SHOULD HELP THEM.
I... I DON'T THINK
THEY NEED ANY HELP.
( screaming )
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]